{
    "exam_questions":[
    {
      "source": "",
      "topic": "",
      "question": "This library is an extension of NavSDK and it reports vehicle location and routing info to Fleet Engine.",
      "type": "option",
      "choices": {
        "A": "Consumer SDK",
        "B": "NavSDK Plus",
        "C": "Driver SDK",
        "D": "Token Factory"
      },
      "answer": "C",
      "page": 0,
      "most_voted": ""
    },
    {
      "source": "",
      "topic": "",
      "question": "This API includes the process of calculating the path along the road network complete with ETA in a performance optimized manner.",
      "type": "option",
      "choices": {
        "A": "Directions API",
        "B": "Autocomplete API",
        "C": "Routes Preferred API",
        "D": "Cloud Fleet Routing"
      },
      "answer": "C",
      "page": 0,
      "most_voted": ""
    },
    {
      "source": "",
      "topic": "",
      "question": "This defines the components and attributes of each use case scenario such as driver status, location information, task status, etc.",
      "type": "option",
      "choices": {
        "A": "Fleet Engine",
        "B": "Data Model",
        "C": "Customer Backend",
        "D": "gRPC bindings"
      },
      "answer": "B",
      "page": 0,
      "most_voted": ""
    },
    {
      "source": "",
      "topic": "",
      "question": "A task will be created inside Fleet Engine by invoking this API when using Driver SDK.",
      "type": "option",
      "choices": {
        "A": "CreateDeliveryTaskRequest.builder",
        "B": "setVehicleStops.builder",
        "C": "NavigationVehicleReporter.enrouteToNextStop",
        "D": "NavigationVehicleReporter.arrivedAtStop"
      },
      "answer": "A",
      "page": 0,
      "most_voted": ""
    },
    {
      "source": "",
      "topic": "",
      "question": "This library is built on top of the Maps SDK and it powers the journey sharing experience.",
      "type": "option",
      "choices": {
        "A": "Consumer SDK",
        "B": "Maps SDK Plus",
        "C": "Driver SDK",
        "D": "Match-making service"
      },
      "answer": "A",
      "page": 0,
      "most_voted": ""
    },
    {
      "source": "",
      "topic": "",
      "question": "What are the 2 core uses of Google Mobility services?",
      "type": "multiple_choice",
      "choices": {
        "A": "ODRD",
        "B": "LMFS",
        "C": "Scheduled",
        "D": "On-Demand"
      },
      "answer": ["C", "D"],
      "page": 0,
      "most_voted": ""
    },
    {
        "source": "",
        "topic": "",
        "question": "This packaged pricing structure will activate better end-to-end mobility experience with efficient routing and improved navigations.",
        "type": "option",
        "choices": {
          "A": "Pay-As-You-Go",
          "B": "Mobility Activate",
          "C": "Mobility Optimize",
          "D": "Mobility Accelerate"
        },
        "answer": "B",
        "page": 0,
        "most_voted": ""
      },
      {
        "source": "",
        "topic": "",
        "question": "In scheduled use case, this library enables the capability to track fleet performance.",
        "type": "option",
        "choices": {
          "A": "Fleet Engine",
          "B": "Fleet Tracking Javascript Library",
          "C": "Consumer SDK for Javascript",
          "D": "Shipment Tracking Javascript Library"
        },
        "answer": "B",
        "page": 0,
        "most_voted": ""
      },
      {
        "source": "",
        "topic": "",
        "question": "This API accepts a user-specified address and finds the best known location for it.",
        "type": "option",
        "choices": {
          "A": "Geocoding API",
          "B": "Location Selection API",
          "C": "Place Autocomplete",
          "D": "Address Validation API"
        },
        "answer": "D",
        "page": 0,
        "most_voted": ""
      },
      {
        "source": "",
        "topic": "",
        "question": "How to trigger a billing transaction?",
        "type": "option",
        "choices": {
          "A": "via Cloud Logging",
          "B": "via Pub/Sub",
          "C": "via Deliveries API",
          "D": "implement customer backend"
        },
        "answer": "C",
        "page": 0,
        "most_voted": ""
      }
  ]
}